<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Janet X. Chen</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Janet X. Chen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Happens to Data after Death?</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/01/what-happens-to-data-after-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/01/what-happens-to-data-after-death/</guid>
      <description>Download the PDF Download the design workbook This study in the news:  Abstract  Digital data has become a key part of everyday life: people manage increasingly large and disparate collections of photos, documents, media, etc. But what happens after death? How can users select and prepare what data to leave behind before their eventual death? To explore how to support users, we first ran an ideation workshop to generate design ideas; then, we created a design workbook with 12 speculative concepts that explore diverging approaches and perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>-- I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in Information Science at Cornell. I earned my BA in computer science and economics at the University of British Columbia. During this time, I worked for 12 months as a software development intern.
I’m interested in understanding data in speculative situations and creating trauma-informed technology experiences. Some of my past work touches on preparing digital data in preparation of death, designing for possible data management futures, and creating AR/VR applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>Last updated: May 2022. 
Education Ph.D Information Science, Cornell University (2020-2025)  Committee: Malte Jung, Karen Levy, Aditya Vashistha 
B.A. Computer Science and Economics, University of British Columbia  Research advisors: Joanna McGrenere, Dongwook Yoon
Publications Trauma-Informed Computing: Towards Safer Technology Experiences for All  Janet X. Chen,* Allison McDonald,* Yixin Zou,* Emily Tseng, Kevin A. Roundy, Acar Tamersoy, Florian Schaub, Thomas Ristenpart, Nicola Dell  ACM CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems, May 2022  * indicates shared first authorship</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
